<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Sandy</string>
  <string name="title_home">Home</string>
  <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
  <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
  <string name="facebook_app_id">314778556117982</string>
  <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb314778556117982</string>
  <string name="first_screen">Hello, my name is Sandy. Before we chow down together, I have to get to know you. Touch my buns to proceed</string>
  <string name="saved_tutorial_complete_key">tutorial_key</string>
  <string name="picture">Picture</string>
  <string name="description_info">Info</string>
  <string name="request_permission">This sample needs camera permission.</string>
  <string name="camera_error">This device doesn\'t support Camera2 API.</string>
  <string name="intro_message">This is an intro message I\'ve included because they voices told me to.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_no0">Watch where you put that finger. I said touch my buns.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_no1">I know who you are and I\'ve seen where you sleep. Do not lie to me again.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_no2">Some people just don\'t appreciate the Chip Butty. Deleting</string>
  <string name="tutorial_no3">That was an ice cream SANDWICH, but I\'ll respect your prejudice - deleting</string>
  <string name="tutorial_no4">Yes, it does appear the chef was missing a step.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_no5">Oh come on, a sub isn\'t a sandwich?! Fine, have it your way.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_no6">Oh really? I always took you for someone who enjoyed a good wiener.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_no7">Yes, the dessert taco does seem like a bit of a stretch</string>
  <string name="tutorial_no8">If you had tried to get cute, that knuckle sandwich would have been for you.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_no9">I take it you\'re more of a structural purist. Small minds fear new ideas.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_no10">I get it; you\'re a two pieces of bread kind of person. Yes, I judging you.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_no11">Had you clicked yes, I would have alerted authorities and had you committed.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_no12">Personally, I love to eat cat. But maybe I\'m a pervert.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_no13">Your answers have been inconsistent. Restarting tutorial</string>
  <string name="tutorial_no14">Congratulations, you have trained me well. Let\'s eat!</string>
  <string name="tutorial_yes0">Mmmmmm. Teach me your ways. Starting Tutorial</string>
  <string name="tutorial_yes1">Confirmed structural purist; ingredient purist. Gleefully stroking my belly.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_yes2">Confirmed Ingredient Neutral with Structural Purity. Salivating.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_yes3">Born to be wild: Ingredient Rebel wth Structural Purity.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_yes4">I have been lied to in the past. That doesn\'t mean it hurts any les when you do it.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_yes5">Confirmed Structural Neutral, Ingredient Pure.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_yes6">Sandwich Equanimity is found in the frank: True Neutral.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_yes7">I love an open mind. Spread that cerebrum, Ingredient Rebel.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_yes8">You keep lying to me, and I\'ll serve a knuckle sandwich self.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_yes9">Willing to put your hands on anything: Structural Rebel, Ingredient Pure.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_yes11">God Help Us. TOTAL SANDWICH ANARCHY.</string>
  <string name="tutorial_yes10">Confirmed Structural Rebel, Ingredient Neutral, and Bona Fide Madman</string>
  <string name="tutorial_yes12">You are an Unholy Monster. I am sending your location to Federal Authorities.</string>
  <string name="auth_fail">unable to authenticate</string>
  <string-array name="tutorial_questions">
    <item>Is this a sandwich?</item>
    <item>Okay smartie, is this a sandwich?</item>
    <item>I don\'t care if you think you could fit this in your mouth\; is it a sandwich?</item>
    <item>Sandwich, or not sandwich? That is the question.</item>
  </string-array>
</resources>
